[hammer tapping]
- Based on the number of taps,
it should be coming
from this direction!
- Up there!
- [Hiraku] Something big
is headed here.
What is that thing?
A dragon?
- No, it's a wyvern!
- It can't be!
[intense music]
[wyvern roaring]
["Flower Ring" by Shino Shimoji
and Aya Suzaki plays]
[intense music]
[wyvern roaring]
[all grunting]
[wind howling]
- We must defend, Lu!
[barrier cracking]
[Lea gasping]
- Hurry, we need to
put out the fires!
[all panting]
- This is bad.
- Yeah.
Should we attack?
I'm not sure we can
pierce its barrier.
[wyvern growling]
[light humming]
[Hiraku gasping]
[energetic rock music]
- Crush him!
- No way!
[Hiraku growling]
[wyvern thudding]
[Lu gasping]
- [Lea] We managed to
put out all the fires.
There was some damage
to the crop fields,
but all of the buildings
are fine.
- [Hiraku] I see.
It looks like I managed
to take it down.
Are there a lot of
these creatures?
- There are some places
where they live,
but running into one of
them that's this large
is a very rare occurrence.
- Is there any possibility
that someone sent this
wyvern here to attack us?
- No, I don't think so.
Even if this wyvern was
under someone's command,
they wouldn't send such a
rare and valuable creature
off on its own to attack.
It's most likely a wild
creature acting alone.
- [Hiraku] I see.
Then I guess we can safely say
that this was nothing more
than a rare incident.
[all sighing anxiously]
By the way...
- What is it, Hiraku?
- Is it okay to eat this?
[cheerful music]
- [Lu] Wyvern meat
is said be a delicacy.
In fact, it is said that
there was once a king
who sent his army into a
den of wyverns to hunt them
and bring them back for
the king to taste for himself.
- [Tia] Great story, Lu,
but I'm pretty sure
that ended with all of them
getting burned to death
and then swallowed whole
by the wyverns, so...
[all exclaiming excitedly]
- Here's the meat in question.
This is a wyvern round steak,
grilled with spices.
I wrapped the breast meat
in leaves and steamed it.
And for the tail meat,
I made a stew with vegetables.
[Lu humming in delight]
- I thought it would be
really tough and gristly,
but this meat,
it's super tender and juicy!
- And to think, a regular
knife couldn't even
pierce its skin,
but now it's so soft!
- This delicacy is just as
delicious as it looks!
- [Lu] I can't understand you.
- This broth tastes amazing!
Every bite of meat I take has
more flavor than the last!
[all humming in delight]
- Hey, you think you could have
blocked Hiraku's spear?
- No, not even close.
That attack pierced a
three-layer barrier
from a wyvern,
and then blew right through
its chest like it was nothing.
- [Lu] Maybe it was
a stroke of luck
that Kuro and the dogs
were who we ran into first
when we came here.
- [Tia] Yeah, you're right.
- What's the matter?
Did I not get all the bones?
- No, it's just we're blessed
to enjoy our meals
in good health.
- That's right.
We thank fate for smiling on us.
- It's no big deal!
- [Tia] This one's
delicious, too!
- [Lu] It really is!
[menacing music]
- [Grattz] You say
a wyvern was taken down?
Enough of these jokes!
- No, the report we
received is true.
- Impossible!
One of those things drawing near
requires that we mobilize
our entire military force!
There's no way...
- He was attacked from the
ground and killed in two hits.
- Absurd!
- Enough of these jokes!
- [Beezel] It's true.
- [growls] We can't fight that!
And we just finished getting
this year's budget approved!
- [Grattz] No...
It's a joke, right?
- [Beezel] Stop saying that.
Now, before panic begins to
spread among our citizens,
it's our job as the generals
to handle this.
- [Randan] I've got it!
Let's resign!
- [Beezel] Please don't.
Don't run away
from this, Randan!
[intense music]
- [Dryme] Did you see it, Gucci?
- Yes, I saw it
with my own eyes.
- And what do you
think would happen
if I were to receive
such an attack?
- It would pierce
cleanly through you.
- What do we do?
- It would be foolish to attack.
- [Dryme] Yes, definitely.
[Hiraku humming thoughtfully]
- The wyvern meat was
every bit as delicious
as it was said to be,
but if I'm being honest,
there's still one thing that
was missing from the meal.
[Lu squealing excitedly]
- Are we going to start now?
- Is it finally time?
- Huh?
Yeah.
We're making alcohol!
[all gasping excitedly]
If we're making alcohol
out of grapes,
then it's going to be wine.
Apparently, wine exists
in this world.
So everyone was excited and
quickly harvested the grapes.
Now all that's left is to
squash the grapes
and let them ferment.
To do that, we built...
this!
- [Lea] We're going to
walk on top of these?
- [Hiraku] Yeah!
Make sure to stomp 'em
real good.
- [Tia] I'm a little hesitant
to stomp on something
that we're going to drink.
- [Hiraku] If you get tired,
you can switch with someone.
- What about you?
- Oh, me? I'm switching the
barrels as they fill up.
By the way,
these barrels were built
by the High Elf Lalasha
because she knows how to
make containers
that are watertight.
I had her make them right away.
All right, you guys
can start now!
- [Lea] Uh...
[grapes squishing]
[Lea yelping]
Wow, you really sink into them.
Am I doing it right?
- Great, now let's see...
Move in a circular motion
around the whole thing.
- Okay!
Let's go in this direction.
- Okay.
[Tia and Lea groaning anxiously]
[Tia yelping]
- Careful not to slip
and fall, Tia!
- Okay!
[Tia grunting]
Oh, no!
[Tia and Lea yelping]
[Hiraku gasping]
[water splashing]
- [Hiraku] Are you all right?
- I think so!
[Tia and Lea sighing]
- Sorry, Tia.
I bumped into you.
- Not at all, that was my fault.
You know, this would be easier
if we had a way
to keep our rhythm.
It might keep all of
our movements in sync.
- [Lea] Good point.
[Leeta gasping excitedly]
- I have an idea, we can use
that song we used to sing.
It helped us before when
we worked in the village.
- Oh, yeah!
That just might work!
- A song from your village?
- Yeah, that's right!
It goes like this!
One, and two, three, go!
[Leeta and Leely
singing in Elvish]
[all singing in Elvish]
[hands tapping]
[Tia yelping]
[Tia laughing]
[hands tapping]
[grapes squishing]
[Tia laughing]
- Looks like they
found their rhythm.
- [Tia] Hey, Lu!
Come on, it's really fun!
- 'Kay.
You're coming, too.
- Huh?
But I'm-
- [Lu] Let's go!
- [Hiraku] Hey, wait!
- [Lu] Come on!
[Hiraku yelping]
That's it!
[all singing]
[all laughing]
[Hiraku sighing]
- That was a lot of work today.
- I'm exhausted,
but that was a lot of fun.
- [Hiraku] Now, the yeast
on the skin of the grapes
should ferment this for us.
I wonder if we made too much.
- I wouldn't worry about it.
- I'm sure we'll have
no problem drinking it all.
- Totally!
I can't wait to drink it!
- Don't tell me
we didn't make enough!
- [God] See?
Look how much fun he's having!
So can't you forgive me already?
- Absolutely not!
You mistakenly punished
an innocent human soul,
and then sneakily
tried to save him,
only to end up sending him
to the dreaded Forest of Death!
[God flinching]
And you gave him that spear!
I can't believe you
gave him a replica
of the Holy Lance Gryme!
- Well, right now, he's only
using it as a farming tool.
Plus, I got permission,
remember?
- [Goddess] You didn't tell me
you were giving that to a human!
That thing will drain
all of their life force
and kill them instantly!
- But he's doing fine right now!
I'm sure it's because he has
super fast recovery abilities
since I gave him such a
healthy body this time around!
- [Goddess] I'm telling you
that you were too careless!
and besides that...
And besides that!
Why is the statue that's
supposed to me
a grizzled old man?
- [God] That is not my fault!
- [Goddess] No excuses!
As punishment, you will sit
like that for 300 years!
- Please forgive me,
my daughter!
[leaves rustling]
[hammer tapping]
[wolves growling]
[Flora whimpering]
- [Hiraku] I'm sensing
deja vu, here.
- Flora?
- My dear sister!
- [Hiraku] They're
actually related?
- [Flora] Yes!
It was not long
after I figured out
that you were being chased
by that black-hearted angel,
I decided to follow you
all the way here.
- Who did you say was
black-hearted?
- [Flora] [yelps]
Why is she here?
It was just an expression!
- [Hiraku] Apparently,
Flora is also a vampire.
And she's related to Lu.
- Please, sister, help me!
- Since you're already
here, why not relax
and stay with us for a while?
- Okay.
I'm having a hard time
believing he's Lu's husband.
Something feels off
about all this.
[wolf growling]
Ah, no, nevermind!
- He's the one in charge here.
And he's the master of
all these inferno wolves.
He even took down
a giant wyvern!
- I see now.
- I'm sorry for my behavior!
- Don't worry about it.
So anyways, you guys
are wolves, Kuro?
I had no idea!
[Kuro growling]
What's the inferno part mean?
[fire roaring]
Wow, that's amazing!
- You've been living
with them this whole time
and didn't know?
- I believe they're
well-known magical beasts.
[Flora gasping excitedly]
- You can think of this
as an apology.
For Kuro and the wolves.
We went ahead and
made dinner for you.
[Flora munching happily]
[Lu chuckling nervously]
- [Flora] It's great!
[sighs] This is fantastic!
What's that soft, white stuff?
- [Hiraku] Oh, that's
called tofu.
After a lot of tries,
I finally got it right.
- [Lu] It's made from
a bean called soybean.
- [Flora] Wow, this is
made from beans?
- Flavoring soup with salt
is fine and all,
but I really wanted some miso.
Plus, I wanted to be able to put
soy sauce on other stuff.
- Miso? And soy sauce?
- [Hiraku] Miso and
soy sauce are made
from fermented soybeans
and help to flavor food.
- Fermented?
- [Hiraku] Basically,
it seems in this world,
fermented foods like
wine and cheese exist.
However, they aren't aware
of the microorganisms
that actually cause
fermentation.
- I see.
If tiny organisms we aren't able
to see with our eyes exist,
and these same organisms
can cause
transformations in matter
without magic,
then that would serve
to explain all of this.
- Come on, eat or talk, Flora.
- It seems that, like Lu,
she's also passionate
about her research.
- I have found a fascinating
new subject for my research!
I will bring the wonders
of miso and soy sauce
to all that I cross!
And then there will
come a day when I will
feast upon miso soup
and cold tofu forever!
- [Hiraku] After staying
a few days,
Flora left with great haste
and excitement
so she could make preparations
to move.
- [Flora] I have returned!
- Okay.
- That was way faster
than I thought.
You even brought
the maids with you.
- Nice to meet you.
My name is Anne, and I speak
on behalf of the other maids
as their rep.
We ask that you put us to use
as you so see fit, master.
- Uh, you don't really need
to be that formal.
By the way, what are those?
I mean, those are just
normal cows, right?
- [Flora] That's right!
I made sure to bring
the right cows with me
that would give us milk.
- Oh!
This is great!
Now we can make
butter and cheese!
[Tia humming thoughtfully]
[Tia gasping]
- [Tia] Excuse me!
- What the-
That's close!
- I need to leave here
for a short while.
- Sure.
I wonder what she's
going off to do.
[cow mooing]
- I have now returned!
- Okay.
- And I have brought my
underlings here with me as well!
- My name is Granmaria.
- I'm Kudel.
- I'm Corone, it's a pleasure
to finally meet you.
- I'm Daga, the representative
of the lizardmen.
- Also... I've prepared
this as well!
[chicken clucking]
It's a chicken!
- Does it breathe fire?
- It does not.
- What about eggs?
- It lays them!
That's great.
[Tia laughs happily]
Thanks to everyone here,
this place got
a lot more civilized.
- For the rooms on
this side, Lamulias,
I want them dusted before
we wash the floors.
- Understood, Miss.
- Oh, sorry for interrupting.
- It's fine.
- [Hiraku] The maids
that arrived
belong to a race of ogres.
I guess it's to be expected
since they're professionals,
but as soon as they showed up,
all our chores got done
a lot faster.
However, the inhabitants
of this world
don't seem to cook any
complicated dishes.
I tried to teach them
all the different methods
of cooking that I knew.
Dressing salads!
Steaming!
- [Maids] Ah!
- [Hiraku] It seems like I got
them interested in cooking
all at once.
[knife tapping]
- [Anne] Dinner is served.
Today, I tried making
a dish of killer rabbit
with fragrant vegetables.
- Oh, wow.
So those things are called
killer rabbits, huh?
This looks wild.
They're all very strong,
despite their appearances.
They display both proper manners
and a bit of power.
Then there are the
angels that Tia brought.
- Now then, you're all to patrol
a different region
of the forest.
- [Hiraku] Granmaria,
Kudel, and Corone.
I was wondering why
they all showed up
in such serious-looking armor.
It seems that after
the wyvern attack,
Tia planned on
having them act as
our security on the premises.
I feel safer having them around.
The lizardmen are
in charge of all labor
that requires strength outdoors.
Thanks to them,
our construction work
is moving even faster now.
By the way, I had
their leader, Daga,
tie a scarf around his arm.
I feel bad, but I'm not able to
tell them apart otherwise.
- I guess that does
make sense in a way.
- Now that I think about it,
this place is really filling up
with people living here.
How many of us are there?
[graph beeping]
A lot.
- [Lea] Hiraku!
I brought all the elves
that were still
wandering the forest!
- [Hiraku] Oh?
Now there are even more?
So are they all women?
Where are the men?
I don't see them.
- There weren't really any men
who survived the human war.
- Oh, wow.
- But that's okay, really.
We can just start making
lots more now!
[elves cheering]
- I hope that works out for you!
I decided not to ask them
how they planned to do it.
- Hey, what's going on here?
- Who knows?
I'm just here because
I was asked to come.
- He said to gather
all the different
representatives here today.
- I wonder if some sort of
terrible problem has arisen.
- [Hiraku] Hey.
Sorry for calling you all
here like this.
There's something I wanna
talk about with all of you.
[all humming questioningly]
Here's the thing.
I want a name for our home here.
- You mean this place?
The farm?
- [Hiraku] Yeah.
At first, it was just
my little hut
and some crop fields,
but then more buildings
started popping up,
and more people
started moving in.
It's like a village now, right?
That's why I wanna come up
with a name for this village.
- I like that idea!
A name for our very own village!
Can't we just name it after you,
since you're the original
founder of the whole place?
- [Hiraku] No.
Then it'd be something like
Hiraku Village or Machio Town.
I don't really like
the sound of that.
- In that case, then,
how about we name it
after the forest we're in?
- That sounds like a good idea!
By the way, what is
this forest called?
- It's the Forest of Death.
- For real? That's scary.
- [Tia] So the Village of Death?
- [Lu] Sounds like a ghost town!
- [Hiraku] It sounds like
it'd have a poisoned swamp.
What is it?
You mean this door, here?
You want me to open it?
[Hiraku grunting]
[door creaking]
The Great Tree Village!
[all humming happily]
[sentimental music]
[fire crackling]
Hello, everyone!
From now on, this place is
the Great Tree Village!
In celebration of this day,
we're going to have a party!
[all cheering]
And no party would be
complete without this!
The first batch of wine
we made here
in the Great Tree Village!
Everyone, enjoy yourselves!
- [Leeta and Leely]
Mayor Hiraku!
- Mayor!
[wolf howling]
[Flora whistling]
- Wait!
No, that's something we need
to decide later, as a group!
- What are you talking about?
You're the only one for the job.
- She's right.
They're already
calling you mayor!
- [Crowd] Mayor Hiraku!
Mayor Hiraku!
- I see.
- [Crowd] Mayor Hiraku!
Mayor Hiraku!
[crowd cheering]
[Hiraku laughing]
[mugs clanking]
[sentimental music]
[Lu sighing]
[crowd murmuring]
[Tia gasping]
[Hiraku humming questioningly]
[Tia grunting]
[hand tapping]
[Tia humming]
[hand tapping rapidly]
["Feel the winds"
by Yui Hizuki plays]
- You're a little drunk
there, huh?
- What's the matter, Hiraku?
You're sitting all by
yourself, zoning out.
- Nothing.
Nothing's the matter.
I was just thinking about
how happy I am.
That this all feels
like a dream.
- This isn't a dream.
All of us will keep living
together, enjoying life.
- Yeah, you're right.
I'd like that.
- Yeah?
Let's toast to
the Great Tree Village!
- Yeah!
- [Hiraku And Tia] Cheers!
[mugs tapping]
- [yawns] No fair!
I'm gonna toast, too,
you black-hearted angel!
- Seriously?
You were pretending to sleep
this whole time?
- [Lu] Come on!
- Very well, then.
- How many years has it been?
- [Tia And Lu] Cheers!
It's been a while
since I've had wine.
It tastes better
than I remember.
- Gimme another!
[crowd cheering and laughing]
- I guess I'll give it
a shot as mayor.
[rustic music playing]